livelingua.com 2018-12-27

# Live Lingua Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Live Lingua collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the following URL's: 

Here after refered to as "Website". This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Live Lingua. 

**Our Commitment To Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name Address Email address Phone number On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a class online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: Name, Address & Phone Number

**The Information We DONT Collect:**

Credit/Debit Card Information / date of birth/ race/ sexual orientation. 

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order for classes or purchases with the Website and only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information for gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a class gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties whatsoever. 

We use information to send information about language learning and about additional products created by Live Lingua or it's parent company (Rayvesoft) that may be useful to you. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our class newsletter or worksheet as well as updates on our new classes and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online here at the Website.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending us an email. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. You also have the option to opt out of any emails sent by Live Lingua or it's related companies. 

**Contacting You**

By contacting Live Lingua, whether through our online forms or directly via email, you are giving them permission to contact you via email. If you sign up for paid lessons you are also giving them permission to contact you with information about your classes, teachers, and any promotions offered by Live Lingua or another business owned by Rayvensoft Corporation (Live Lingua's parent company). Live Lingua will never sell your emails to a 3rd party. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: Live Lingua

http:/www.livelingua.com  
24 Birchbrow Ave  
Weymouth, MA  
02191  
USA  
339-499-4390  
info@livelingua.com

This document was last updated on December 13th, 2016
